Guide to the Marilyn Skolnick Papers, 1952-2009 AIS.2001.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Environmental Issues, 1970-2002; I.
  - Air Quality, 1987-2002; 2.
    - Miscellaneous, General Electric Transportation Systems Testimony, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Miscellaneous, Grass Roots Activism, 1987-1999 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Miscellaneous, ISTEA, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Miscellaneous, Kosmos Cement, 1990-1992 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Miscellaneous, Mid-Atlantic Air Management Association, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Miscellaneous, Mobility/Air Quality, Baltimore Meeting, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Miscellaneous, National Toxics Campaign Fund, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Miscellaneous, Newsletters, 1993-1997 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Miscellaneous, Nine Mile Run Task Committee, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Miscellaneous, Northeast States Coordinated Air Use Management, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Miscellaneous, PennDOT, 1988-1996 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Miscellaneous, PennDOT, Air Quality Program Development Support, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 54-55)
    - Miscellaneous, Pennsylvania Environmental Network, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Miscellaneous, PEAC Conference Call, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Miscellaneous, Photochemical Air Quality Modeling, undated (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Miscellaneous, Pittsburgh Cancer Institute, undated (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Miscellaneous, Rail Superior to Truck on Energy Consumption, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Miscellaneous, STPP, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Miscellaneous, Surface Mining Reclamation and Enforcement, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Miscellaneous, Title V. Permitting, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Miscellaneous, TIP Conformity Analysis, Lackawanna Valley Industrial, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Miscellaneous, Toxics Release Inventory Information, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Miscellaneous, U.S. DOT, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Miscellaneous, University of Pittsburgh, Center for Hazardous Materials, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Miscellaneous, Voluntary Investigation and Cleanup Program, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Miscellaneous, Work Group Participants/Contacts, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Miscellaneous, VIP2 Business Interest Survey, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Ozone, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Ozone, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Ozone, Pennsylvania, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Ozone, Newspaper Articles, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Ozone Stakeholders, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Ozone Stakeholders, October 1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Ozone Stakeholders, October 2002 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Ozone Stakeholders, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Ozone Stakeholders, Alpine Geophysics, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Ozone Stakeholders, Alpine Geophysics, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Ozone Stakeholders, CDR Associates, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Ozone Stakeholders, Meetings, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Ozone Stakeholders, I/M Working Group, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Ozone Stakeholders, I/M Working Group, Members, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Ozone Transport Commission, 1992-1996 (Box 7, Folder 12-13)
    - Pittsburgh Ozone Stakeholders Working Group, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 14-20)
    - Pittsburgh Ozone Stakeholders Working Group, Organizational Meeting, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Pittsburgh Ozone Stakeholders Working Group, Regional Attainment Study, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - SWPA Growth Alliance, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - SWPA, Ozone Stakeholders Working Group, July/August 1996 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - SWPA, Ozone Stakeholders Working Group, Members, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - SWPA, Ozone Stakeholders Working Group, August 1996 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - SWPA, Ozone Stakeholders Working Group, November 1996 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - SWPA, Ozone Stakeholders Working Group, December 1996 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - SWPA, Ozone Stakeholders Working Group, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - SWPA, Ozone Stakeholders Working Group, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - SWPA, Ozone Stakeholders Working Group, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - SWPA, Ozone Stakeholders Working Group, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - SWPA, Ozone Stakeholders Working Group, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - SWPA, Ozone Stakeholders Working Group, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - SWPA, Ozone Stakeholders Working Group, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - SWPA, Ozone Stakeholders Working Group, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - SWPA, Ozone Stakeholders Working Group, Action Partnership, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - SWPA, Ozone Stakeholders Working Group, Action Partnership, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - SWPA, Ozone Stakeholders Working Group, Rules and Jobs, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Smog, 1988-1991 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - U.S. Steel, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - VIP2, 1992-1996 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - VIP2, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - VIP2, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - VIP2, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - VIP2, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - VIP2, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - VIP2, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - VIP2, Annual Report Draft, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - VIP2, Program Initiatives, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Working Group on Community Right to Know, Undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Allegheny County Local Emergency Planning Committee (LEPC), 1982-2002; 3.
    The documents in this subseries date from 1982 to 2002 and are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - 1982-2000 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - 1984-1990 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - 1988-1991 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 27-28)
    - 1990 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - 1992 (Box 8, Folder 30-31)
    - 1992-2001 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - 1993-2002 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - 1994-1996 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - 1994-1997 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - 1994-2000 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - 1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - 1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - 1996-2000 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - 1997-2000 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - 2001 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Air Pollution, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Air Pollution, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Corporate Response, 1989-1998 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Emergency Service Incidents, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Environmental Spotlight, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Grassroots Particulates Report, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 15-16)
    - Local/Finance Subcommittee, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Literature, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - New England Journal of Medicine, Particulate Air Pollution, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Plans and Updates, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Regional Air Quality Workshop, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Alternative Fuels, 1996; 4.
    The documents in the Alternative Fuels subseries date from 1996.
    - Data Center, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Chemicals, 1987-2000; 5.
    The documents in the Chemicals subseries date from 1987 to 2000 and are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - ACHD, Air Toxics Subcommittee, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - ACHD, Air Toxics Subcommittee, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - ACHD, SO2 Conference, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Annual Pittsburgh Chemical Day, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, James Seif, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, Risk Policy Report, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Hazardous Chemicals, Accidents Waiting to Happen, Bhopal, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Hazardous Materials Emergency Response, Allegheny County, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Hazardous Materials, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Hazardous Materials, Emergency Planning and Response, 1997-2000 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Hazardous Substances and Public Health, 1993-2001 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Lead, U.S. Department of Labor, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Methane, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Non-Toxic Alternatives, undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Pesticides and Chemicals, undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Radon, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Subcommittee on Permits and Toxics Integrations, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - TRI Data, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Toxics, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Toxics Use Reductions Council Resolutions, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - U.S. Chemical Safety and Hazard Investigation Board, Sierra Chemical Company, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Methyl, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Chambers Landfill Company, 1972-1999; 6.
    The materials in this subseries date from 1972 to 1999 and are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - 1975-1978 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - 1987-1990 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - 1988 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - 1988-1991 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - 1988-1995 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - 1992 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - ACHD, Air Sampling, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - ACHD, Correspondence, 1988-1995 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - ACHD, Notice of Violations, 1982-1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - ACHD, Notice of Violation, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - ACHD, Report of Violations, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Chambers Development Company, 1975-1982 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Chambers Development Company, Appeal, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Chambers Development Company, Memos, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Chambers Development Company, Proposed Consent Decree, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Chambers Development Company, Reports, 1974-1992 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Chambers Development Company, Roadway Access Study, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Chambers Landfill, Activities, 1991-1994 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Chambers Landfill Permit, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Chambers Landfill, Property Evaluation Impact Study, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Chambers Landfill, Public Notice, the Pittsburgh Press, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Chambers Landfill, Statements, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Citizens for a Good Environment, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Citizens for a Good Environment, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Citizens for a Good Environment, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Citizens for a Good Environment, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 22-23)
    - Citizens for a Good Environment, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 24-25)
    - Citizens for a Good Environment, Exhibit A, Maps, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Citizens for a Good Environment, Newsletter, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Citizens for a Good Environment, Request to be a party, correspondence, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Citizens for a Good Environment, Response to Chambers Closure Land Use Plan, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Citizens for a Good Environment, Statement before Monroeville Council, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, Washington C. Alston, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, Chambers Development to ACHD, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, City Council, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, Consent Decree, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, Lee R. Golden Esquire, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, Shelly Kaltenbaugh, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence, Skolnick, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 37-40)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, 1996-1999 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, Correspondence, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, Air Quality Criteria, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, Air Quality Permitting Criteria, undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, Air Toxics Policy, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, Commissioned Methane Study, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, Notice of Violations and Warnings, 1976-1990 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, Proposed Air Quality Compliance, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, Proposed Procedures for Public Participation, undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, Reports on Chambers Issues to be Resolved, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, Results of Methane Sampling, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, Project Summary, Controlling Landfill Emissions, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Gas Probe Monitoring Results, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Legal, 1988-1993 (Box 10, Folder 59-60)
    - Legal, No. 2124, Attorney, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Legal, No. 2124, Attorney, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Legal, No. 2124, Attorney Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Legal, No. 2124, Civil Division, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 64-65)
    - Legal, No. 2124, Anthony Petrulli versus Chambers, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 66-67)
    - Legal, No. 2124, filing by Dodero Kenedy and Cambest, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Legal, No. 2124, Notice of Appeal for Oral Argument, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Legal, No. 2410, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Legal, Act 101, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Legal, Closure Plan, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Legal, Closure Plan Revised, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Legal, Closure Land Use Plan and Compliance History, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Legal, Compliance History, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Legal, Compliance History, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Legal, Consent Agreement, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Legal, Consent Decree, Joint Motion to Approve No. 2415, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Legal, Consent Decree, PA DER and ACHD, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Legal, Court of Common Pleas, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Legal, Exhibits, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Legal, General, Chambers Freedom of Information Act, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Legal, General, Chambers Plaintiff versus Monroeville Defendant No. GD 80-31208, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Legal, General, Correspondence Citizens for a Good Environment, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Legal, General, Gas Probe Monitoring Results, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Legal, General, Memorandum Opinion, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Legal, General, Monroeville Ordinance 1443, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Legal, General, Notice of Reschedule for Arguments, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Legal, General, Pitcairn versus Monroeville, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Legal, General, Skolnick Notes and Information, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Legal, General, Statement before the Citizen's Advisory Council, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Legal, General, Statement in Absence of Transcript, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Legal, General, Testimony of Jerry Borst, undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Legal, General, Permit Modification Application, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Legal, General, Permit Modification, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Legal, General, Property Identification Plan, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Legal, General, Response to Request for Reconsideration, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Legal, General, Violations, 1979-1990 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Legal, General, Zoning Map, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Monroeville Advisory Committee, undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Monroeville Agreement with Chambers (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Monroeville Appeal, Denial of Zoning Applications, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Monroeville Citizen Action, 1987-1991 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Monroeville Council, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Monroeville Council Action, 1972-1990 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Monroeville Council Meeting, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Monroeville Council, CGE Statement, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Monroeville Council, CGE Statement, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Monroeville Council Correspondence, Lee to Skolnick, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Monroeville, Chambers Appeal, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Monroeville, Emergency Response Meeting, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Monroeville, Exhibit versus Chambers, undated (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Monroeville, Home Rule Charter, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Monroeville, Gas Management System, undated (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Monroeville, Memos and Agenda, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Monroeville, Ordinance, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Monroeville, Ordinance 1443, undated (Box 11, Folder 50-51)
    - Monroeville, Ordinance 1843, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Monroeville, Planning Commission Minutes, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Monroeville, Press Release, undated (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - News clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - News clippings, 1988-1992 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - News clippings, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Notes, 1988-1992 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Press Releases, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Reports, Ambient Air Testing, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Reports, Closure Plan, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Reports, Dobos House Explosion, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Reports, History, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Reports, Human Needs, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Reports, Independent Press Release, undated (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Reports, Landfill Expansion, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Reports, Luthy, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Reports, Maps of Monitoring Areas, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Reports, Maps of Surrounding Community, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Reports, Miscellaneous, Assorted Landfills, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Reports, Miscellaneous, Chambers Low Interest Loan, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Reports, Miscellaneous, Official General Election Results, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Reports, Miscellaneous, PA Bulletin Vol. 18 No. 15, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
    - Reports, Miscellaneous, USA Waste Services Annual Meeting, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Reports, Miscellaneous, USA Waste Services Letter to Stakeholders, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Reports, Miscellaneous, USA Waste Services Merger, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Reports, Miscellaneous, Wilbur Smith Associates, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Reports, Radius of Influence Testing, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Reports, Rizzo Engineering Review of Expansion, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Reports, Soil Samples, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Reports, Stack Height, 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Reports, Testimony, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Economy, 1994; 7.
    The documents in this subseries date from 1994.
    - Campaign for an Environmental Economy, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Council on Economic Priorities, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Global Economy, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Endangered Species, 1999; 8.
    The materials in this subseries date from 1999.
    - Allegheny Group Endangered Species, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Energy, 1987-2000; 9.
    The documents in the Energy subseries date from 1987 to 2000 and are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Antaeus Energy, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Coal, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Electric Power Research Institute, 1990-1996 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Energy, 1993-1999 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Environment and Energy Issues Update, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Environmental Resources and Energy Committee, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Oil and Gas, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Pennsylvania Mining Program and Reclamation Activities, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - PM Report, the Annapolis Center, undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Pittsburgh Energy Technology Center Journal, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 32-33)
    - Project Status Report, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Seminar, the Future of Energy in Pennsylvania, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - U.S. Department of Energy, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - U.S. Department of Energy, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - U.S. Department of Energy, undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Environmental Education, 1997-2001; 10.
    The materials in the Environmental Education subseries date from 1997 to 2001 and are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - ACHD Education Subcommittee, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - PA DEP, Environmental Assistance Network Project, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - PA DEP, Environmental Education Grants Program, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Environmental Protection Agency Updates, 1995-2001; 11.
    The documents in the Environmental Protection Agency Updates subseries date from 1995 to 2001 and are arranged by year.
    - 1993-1998 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - 1995 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - 1995-1999 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - 1996 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - 1997-2000 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - 1997-2001 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - 1998 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - 1998-2002 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - 1999-2001 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - General Environment, 1986-2002; 12.
    The materials in the General subseries date from 1986 to 2002 and are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - 1987-1993 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - 1987-1997 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - 1988-1998 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - 1989-1995 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - 1989-1998 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - 1991-1996 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - 1992-1997 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - 1992-1997 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - 1993-1996 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - 1993-1996 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - 1993-2000 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - 1993-2001 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - 1994 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - 1994-1996 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - 1994-1996 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - 1995 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - 1995-1997 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - 1996 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - 1996-2000 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - 1997 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - 1997-1999 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - 1998 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - 2001 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - 21st Century Environment Commission, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
    - Act 97, Speech, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Allegheny County, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Bicycles and Pedestrians, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Bicycles and Pedestrians, Public Participation Report, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Biodiversity, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Citizens Advisory Council, Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Citizens for a Good Environment, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Citizens for a Good Environment, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Citizens for a Good Environment Agenda, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Citizens for a Good Environment Newsletter, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Citizens Fund, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Citizens Helping Our Community, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Citizens Helping Our Community, Membership List, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Civil Action, Class Action versus Carol Browner, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 18)